(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
スクリーンショット・SNSへの投稿もOK！
Feel free to share screenshots and reactions
on social media!
ハッシュタグ #ReGLOSS1stLive で盛り上がりましょう！
Use the hashtag #ReGLOSS1stLive
and join the conversation!
録音、録画、ミラー配信や
違法アップロードは固くお断りいたします
Audio, video recordings, mirror streams,
and illegal uploads are strictly prohibited.
ATTENTION ご来場のお客様へ
ATTENTION To the visitors
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights
during the performance.
声出し応援 OK です
Cheering loudly is OK.
Flashpoint ReGLOSS 1st Live
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will start soon.
演出の都合上、照明の明滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is OK.
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will start soon.
どアニメ宣言！JOYSOUND
Do Anime Sengen! JOYSOUND
アニメにハマって、歌いたくなっちゃった。
I've really gotten into anime, and now I want to sing.
推しのシーン見ながらカラオケ歌えるなんて、
To be able to sing karaoke while watching my favorites...
尊すぎてツライ！
...it's so precious, it hurts!
歌いたいアニメ・ゲームソング見つけよう！
Find the anime and game songs you want to sing!
Joysound!
ReGLOSS 2nd Album 「Snapshot」の
ReGLOSS 2nd Album "Snapshot"'s
レコードとカセットテープが
vinyl and cassette tapes
2026年2月25日より
from February 25, 2026,
HMV限定で発売決定しました！
are confirmed for release exclusively at HMV!
12月17日いっぱいまでにご予約いただくと
Pre-order by the end of December 17th
期間限定予約特典として
to receive a limited-time pre-order bonus
スマホサイズステッカーをプレゼント！
of a smartphone-sized sticker!
さらに抽選で5名様に
In addition, 5 winners chosen by lottery
サイン入りポスターをプレゼント！
will receive a signed poster!
HMV、ReGLOSS、レコード、カセットで検索！
Search for HMV, ReGLOSS, vinyl, and cassette!
以上！
That is all!
ReGLOSSでした〜！！
We were ReGLOSS!!
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is OK.
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
ATTENTION
ご来場のお客様へ
To our audience
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights
during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is OK.
本日は、ReGLOSS 1st Live...
Today, for ReGLOSS 1st Live...
...「Flashpoint」にご来場いただき、ありがとうございます！
..."Flashpoint," thank you for coming!
Reach the top! We are ReGLOSS!
はい！ReGLOSSです！
Hi! We are ReGLOSS!
最後までライブを楽しんでいただくために、いくつかご案内させていただきます。
To ensure everyone enjoys the live show until the end, we have a few announcements.
公演中の撮影、録音、録画機材の使用は固くお断りいたします。
Photography, recording, and the use of recording equipment during the performance are strictly prohibited.
万が一、具合が悪くなってしまった場合は、無理をせず、近くのスタッフへお知らせください。
If you happen to feel unwell, please don't overdo it and let a nearby staff member know.
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、大きく飛び跳ねる、ステージにもの...な...
Mosh pits, diving, jumping excessively, throwing things at the stage... n-...
大丈夫、大丈夫！
It's okay, it's okay!
すみませんね、あの収録とかじゃないんで。
Sorry, it's not like this is a recording or anything.
緊張してるね。
You're nervous, aren't you?
緊張しちゃいました、ごめんなさい。もう一回行きます。ごめんなさい。
I got nervous, I'm sorry. I'll go again. Sorry.
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、大きく飛び跳ねる、ステージにものを投げ込むなど、他のみんなの迷惑になったり公演を妨げる行為は一切禁止です。ルールを守って盛り上がってくださいね！
Mosh pits, diving, jumping excessively, and throwing things onto the stage are all strictly prohibited as they bother others and disrupt the show. Please follow the rules and have a blast!
また、本公演は映像配信および写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、客席が映り込む場合がございます。
Also, cameras for video streaming and photography are in the venue, so the audience may be captured on film.
映像や写真はプロモーションなどに使用される可能性がございますので、あらかじめご了承ください。
Please be aware that the footage and photos may be used for promotions and other purposes.
ライブのハッシュタグは #リグロス1stライブ です。
The hashtag for the live is #ReGLOSSFirstLive.
ハッシュタグを使ってたくさん盛り上げて下さい！
Please use the hashtag and get everyone hyped!
それでは開演までもう少々！
Well then, just a little longer until the show starts!
盛り上がる準備はできてますかー？！
Are you ready to get hyped?!
みんなで一緒に盛り上がるぞー！
Let's all get hyped together!
以上、ReGLOSSでした！
That's all from ReGLOSS!
Don't you get away... wake up people
I don't care... wake up people
どんな視線も釘付け Pretty Girl. OK.
Every gaze is fixed on us, Pretty Girl. OK.
一人じゃ足りないこの声より The Self
More than just this one voice, the self
いた高みの私 Command G
The me at the peak... Command G
今そばにいるけれど妙に
I'm right here beside you, but oddly
面白いフラグが
there's an interesting flag
胸踊る巡り合いは
An exciting encounter
舞一期舞一会
Dancing once in a lifetime
全部優しさで包み込む
Wrapping everything in kindness
上げろ上げて... (Agero Agete!)
Raise it up, raise it up! (Agero Agete!)
うつろい色あせるように... 秘密の奥...
As it shifts and fades... deep within a secret...
××× 〇〇〇 ... 10歳
X X X O O O ... 10 years old
儚いね笑って Enjoy
It's fleeting, isn't it? Just smile and enjoy
踊ってみたサマー アルゴリズムの中
I tried dancing this summer in the algorithm
三叉で旅して
Traveling through the fork in the road
立ち上がるもの 解いた絆を
Those who stand up, the bonds untied
決してしまわないこと... 壊しよ
Don't ever let it end... destroy it
この世界を変えていくよ
I'm going to change this world
きっと好きじゃないけど 君の中の世界なら変えられるはず
I probably won't like it, but if it's the world inside you, it should be changeable
夏咲いてみて 実って枯れて 誰一人はぐれないから
Bloom in summer, ripen and wither, because no one will be left behind
最後に君が笑ってくれれば もうそれだけでいい
If you smile at the end, that's all I need
音乃瀬奏
Otonose Kanade
一条莉々華
Ichijou Ririka
儒烏風亭らでん
Juufuutei Raden
轟はじめ
Todoroki Hajime
Ah~
My heart stars 秘密に 火を灯した心情
My heart stars, in secret, emotions that lit a fire
様変わりして頂戴
Please transform completely
全然悪くないイマジネーション
Not a bad imagination at all
期待通り晴れ渡って
It cleared up just as expected
悲しみに別れを告げる
Telling sadness goodbye
Sleep tight my daydream 踊り出して
Sleep tight my daydream, start dancing
滲む空 低くはバラ色
The blurring sky, the low parts are rose-colored
どれだけ眩ませようとしても
No matter how much I try to dazzle
君がいなければ何の意味もない
It means nothing without you
擦り傷すらつかない幻想
An illusion where not even a scratch occurs
針の落ちないレコードさ
A record with no needle dropping
大概止め処ない追い風背にして
Turning my back to the mostly endless tailwind
Come on, let's go!
相当やり合える向かい風に向かう心
A heart facing a headwind that can really be fought
なびかせて
Letting it flutter
飛び乗ってスカイハイフューチャー
Jump on into the sky-high future
フライングしたってお構いなしさ　ザ・ライト
I don't care if I jump the gun, into the light
ときめいてしまえば
Once your heart starts racing
瞬く間に広がる開放感
A sense of freedom spreads in the blink of an eye
一つつなげてパノラマ
Connect them one by one into a panorama
街中が目覚めてくスタァライト
The whole town awakens, starlight
変わる変わる色のパノラマ
A panorama of ever-changing colors
満ち溢れるフィーリング　アテンション
Overflowing with feelings, attention
始まりのその時が来た
The moment of the beginning has come
Nothing is impossible
目指す　惹かれてく世界
Aiming for a world I'm drawn to
ここ先はまだ誰も知らない世界
From here on is a world no one knows yet
五感してるだけじゃつまんない
Just using five senses is boring
リアルタイムで通じ合って
Connecting in real time
不意に書き換えるモーション
Suddenly rewriting the motion
異常なスピードも I don't mind
I don't mind even unusual speeds
予測できないシチュエーション
An unpredictable situation
どこまで行ってみたい
How far do you want to go?
センチメンタルはない Get far away
No sentimentality, get far away
共に声を鳴らして
Let's make our voices ring out together
肌を貫くような真っ直ぐな痛みが伴っても
Even if it's accompanied by a sharp pain that pierces the skin
この仲間たちと最果てまで Keep running to the end
With these friends, to the ends of the earth, keep running to the end
飛び乗ってスカイハイフューチャー
Jump on into the sky-high future
フライングしたってお構いなしさ　ザ・ライト
I don't care if I jump the gun, into the light
ときめいてしまえば
Once your heart starts racing
瞬く間に広がる開放感
A sense of freedom spreads in the blink of an eye
一つつなげてパノラマ
Connect them one by one into a panorama
街中が目覚めてくスタァライト
The whole town awakens, starlight
変わる変わる色のパノラマ
A panorama of ever-changing colors
満ち溢れるフィーリング　アテンション
Overflowing with feelings, attention
飛び出せユアセルフアップ
Jump out, lift yourself up
恐れるものはないスタァライト
There's nothing to fear, starlight
照らし出せ夜明けが
Let the dawn shine through
透明な明日を運んでる
It's bringing a transparent tomorrow
Mr. Starlight
皆さんこんにちはー！
Hello everyone!
こんにちはー！
Hello!
ReGLOSS 1st Live "Flashpoint"へようこそお越しくださいました！
Welcome to ReGLOSS 1st Live "Flashpoint"!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
今日は皆さん楽しんでいって、素敵な一夜にいたしましょう！
Let's all have fun today and make it a wonderful night!
今日は生バンドでお届けいたします！盛り上がっていきましょう！
Today we're performing with a live band! Let's get fired up!
みんな、次の曲は『マニック』だよー！
Everyone, the next song is 'Manic'!
盛り上がる準備はいいですかー？
Are you ready to get excited?
みんなでウキウキしてね！
Let's all have a thrill together!
Okidoki 女才(おのこ)あなどれり
Okidoki, don't underestimate women's talent
Easy Breezy 歌い出しはマイフェイバリット
Easy Breezy, the beginning of the song is my favorite
Okidoki 自由自在でいたいよね
Okidoki, I want to be free and easy
Easy Breezy 踊るわよ Everybody
Easy Breezy, I'm going to dance, everybody
だれだれがどうなった？　勝ち誇るも誇るも
Who became what? Boasting of victory
精も出せばモチワラえば　無理げーだって勝つ
If you put in the effort and laugh, you can win an impossible game
ときわりない朝から始まる　愉快な仲間
A cheerful bunch starting from a timeless morning
ケースケバ・ハイマイサー　無駄話もひと時　バズコースウォッチ
K-S-K-B High My Sir, idle talk for a moment, buzz course watch
運命共鳴　伝染してゆく喜怒哀楽
Destiny resonance, emotions that become contagious
分かち合える場所　共に目指そう
A place where we can share, let's aim for it together
Reach the top yeah
絶対絶対絶対絶対的キラチューン
Absolute, absolute, absolute, absolute killer tune
今は自由気まま　ビビるなよユニバース
Now I'm free and easy, don't be scared, Universe
リロリロリロリロ進行しろシラフ
Rilo-rilo-rilo-rilo, progress while sober
限界突破　引きつけるミラクル
Breaking limits, attracting miracles
みんなー！後ろの方までよく見えてるよー！
Everyone! I can see you clearly even in the back!
次はまだちょっとブンブン振っていけー！
Next, let's keep waving them like crazy!
Okidoki 女才(おのこ)あなどれり
Okidoki, don't underestimate women's talent
Easy Breezy 歌い出しはマイフェイバリット
Easy Breezy, the beginning of the song is my favorite
Okidoki 自由自在でいたいよね
Okidoki, I want to be free and easy
Easy Breezy 歌い出しはマイフェイバリット
Easy Breezy, the beginning of the song is my favorite
独り占めだった真夜中に
In the midnight that I used to have all to myself
見つけたんだ　同じ気持ち
I found it, the same feeling
押し寄せ あっという間のストーリー
みんなと一緒のライブだエクストラ！
A story that rushes by in an instant.
It's an extra-special live with everyone!
量産されるかけがえのないメモリ
さらに胸掴み 誰にも譲れないディール
Irreplaceable memories being mass-produced.
It grips my heart, a deal I won't give to anyone.
運命 共鳴 全然終点行く道 アイラック
Destiny, resonance, the path to the end, I-luck.
分かっちゃえーる エンパシー たまに目指すわ
I understand your empathy, and sometimes I'll aim for it.
Reach for the top yeah!
絶対絶対絶対的にキラチュン
Absolutely, absolutely, absolute Killer Tune.
今は自由気ままに水入らず
Right now, it's just us, free and easy.
つなぐユニバース リロリロリロ シンクロしちゃう
Connecting the universe, reload-load-load, syncing up.
限界突破で見せつけろミラクル
Break through the limits and show them a miracle.
Okey Dokey 超最高なマイウェイズ
Okey Dokey, my super-awesome my-ways.
Easy Breezy 大体全部フェイバリット
Easy Breezy, pretty much everything's a favorite.
Okey Dokey このままでいたいよね
Okey Dokey, I want things to stay like this.
Easy Breezy 踊ろうよエブリバディ
Easy Breezy, let's dance, everybody!
ReGLOSS 1st Live "Flashpoint"へようこそー！
Welcome to ReGLOSS 1st Live "Flashpoint"!
いつもの挨拶からいきましょう！
Let's start with our usual greeting!
Reach for the top, we are ReGLOSS!
では早速自己紹介からしていきたいと思います！
Now, we'd like to start with our self-introductions!
はーい！ 奏からやりたーい！
Yeah! I want to go first!
おねがいしまーす！
Go ahead!
ドドドすごーい！ 奏に拍手しろー！
Super-duper amazing! Applaud for Kanade!
ホロライブデバイス所属、ReGLOSSの音楽家から、
音乃瀬奏でーす！
From Hololive DEV_IS, the musician of ReGLOSS,
I'm Otonose Kanade!
みんな会えて嬉しいよ！ 見に来てくれてありがとう！
I'm so happy to see everyone! Thank you for coming!
そして！ 可愛いポジティブジーニアス！
And next! The cute, positive genius!
リリカです！ 一条リリカだよー！
I'm Ririka! Ichijou Ririka da yo!
やばいもうみんなの声めっちゃ今浴びてる今！
Oh my god, I'm literally bathing in your voices right now!
めっちゃ嬉しい！ ありがとう！ 最高な気分！
I'm so happy! Thank you! I feel amazing!
はい、えー、ホロライブデバイスReGLOSSの
にぎやかしネタ作り担当、
Hello, everyone. From Hololive DEV_IS ReGLOSS,
in charge of hype and gags,
儒不廷一門は前座見習い、儒烏風亭らでんでございます。
本日はどうぞよろしくお願い申し上げます。
a zenza apprentice of the Juufuutei family,
I'm Juufuutei Raden. It's a pleasure to be here today.
最高！ ハイぷぷぷー！
フライト間近、デスタリコッツォン、番長！
Awesome! Hi pupupu! Almost time for flight,
destaricozzon, Bancho!
突き進め、チバの民！ 皆さんこんちくわー！
Charge forward, people of Chiba! Hello, everyone!
紫ありがとう！
Thanks for the purple!
ついに始まりました！ ReGLOSS 1st Live！
It's finally started! ReGLOSS 1st Live!
なんと会場はここ有明アリーナ！
And the venue is right here at Ariake Arena!
こんなにたくさんのグロッサーが集まってくれましたー！
So many Glossers have gathered here for us!
すごい！ もう最高な景色ですよ皆さん、
ありがとうございます！
Amazing! This is such a wonderful view, everyone.
Thank you so much!
思い思いのファッションとかもね、お目々に見えてね、
フィーリングラデーションの時ちょっとテンションが爆上がりしてしまいましたけども。
I can see everyone's unique outfits,
and my excitement just exploded during 'Feeling Gradation'.
本当にありがとうございます！
今日は最後まで思いっきり楽しんでまいりましょう！
Thank you all so much!
Let's have a blast until the very end today!
そしてね、会場だけじゃなくて、配信もされております！
And, it's not just the venue; it's also being streamed!
配信の皆さん、楽しんでますかー？
Everyone on the stream, are you having fun?
そしてそして、韓国ではライブビューイングが実施されています！
And on top of that, there's a live viewing being held in Korea!
アンニョンハセヨー！
Annyeonghaseyo!
라이브 뷰잉으로 보시는 여러분,
재미있게 즐기고 계신가요?
Everyone watching via live viewing,
are you having a good time?
すごい奏！
That was great, Kanade!
ということで早速ですが、今立っているこのステージではなく、
Now then, we didn't start on this stage where we're standing,
なんと2階からの登場でございましたが、
皆さんびっくりした？ どうだった？
but actually appeared from the second floor!
Were you surprised? How was it?
オープニングから『Feeling Gradation』、そして『Baddies』と
2曲続けてお披露目させていただきましたが、皆さんいかがでしたか？
We performed 'Feeling Gradation' and 'Baddies' back-to-back
from the opening. How did you like them?
そしてね、皆さんもお気づきかと思いますけども、
今回のライブはバンドメンバーと一緒にお届けしています！
And, as you've probably noticed,
we're performing with a live band for this concert!
普段聞いてるあの曲が、どんなアレンジになるのか、お楽しみに！
Look forward to hearing how your favorite songs
have been rearranged!
今日の感想や心に残った瞬間をハッシュタグ
「#ReGLOSS_1stLive」で是非ポストしてください！
Please post your thoughts and favorite moments from today
using the hashtag #ReGLOSS_1stLive!
皆さんの感想、後で我々見に行きますので、
めちゃくちゃ楽しみです！ よろしくお願いします！
We'll be checking your posts later, so we're really
looking forward to them! Thank you!
それでは早速ではございますが、次の曲に行きましょうか！
Well then, without further ado, let's move on to the next song!
あ、でも待って待って待って！
Ah, but wait, wait, wait!
YouTubeやTikTokで見聞きしてくれてる皆さん、ごめんなさい！
To everyone watching on YouTube and TikTok, I'm sorry!
無料パートはここまでになります！
The free portion of the stream ends here!
めっちゃ早いんだけど、無料チラ見せパート
It's so fast, but the free preview part...
なんとですね、次の曲までとなっております！
...is actually up to the next song!
まだまだ一緒に盛り上がりたいみんなは
For those who want to keep getting excited together...
概要欄のリンクから見てください！
...please check the link in the description!
はい！
Yes!
みんなー！
Everyone!
ライブはね、まだまだ
The live concert...
始まったばかりでちゅよ！
...has only just begun!
最後までね、一緒に
Let's make the best time together...
最高な時間をちゅくろ！
...until the end!
おー！
Yeah!
Snowfall 触れる直感 空想と過ちのノイズを鳴らす
Snowfall, a fleeting intuition, sounding the noise of fantasy and error
Slowmo かじかむ衝動 おどけて見せる世界
Slow-mo, a numbing impulse, a world shown in jest
If the sky is falling down
If the stars have no shine
真っさらな紙の上 答え滲ませ
On a blank sheet of paper, the answer bleeds out
全て思うままに
Exactly as I desire
風が刻む 涙のメロディ
The wind carves a melody of tears
パンドラパンドラ 夢を掘り舞い
Pandora, Pandora, digging up and dancing with dreams
移ろい色褪せぬように
So as not to fade and change
パンドラパンドラ 秘密のオブジェ
Pandora, Pandora, an object of secrets
Scarab 嗚呼 パンパンパンパンパン
Scarab, ah, pan-pan-pan-pan-pan
灯す火が サイレンスプラウト
The lighting fire, Silent Sprout
Scarab
1クールのドラマよりも長いフェアリーテイル
A fairy tale longer than a one-season drama
嘘偽りなく Take this pain 殺風景なプラスチックマインド
Truthfully, take this pain, a bleak plastic mind
この世に表も裏もない
In this world, there is no front or back
いつも違う表情 朧げなアイロニー
Always a different expression, a hazy irony
一日を抱きしめてたいのに
Even though I want to embrace the day
In the wall where no one's heart
曖昧の向こう Become kind
Beyond the ambiguity, become kind
忍ばせて仮初め 朽ちるまで待ちぼうけ
Keep it hidden temporarily, waiting until it rots
いずれ花になれ
Eventually, become a flower
風が刻む 涙のメロディ
The wind carves a melody of tears
パンドラパンドラ 夢を掘り舞い
Pandora, Pandora, digging up and dancing with dreams
移ろい色褪せぬように
So as not to fade and change
パンドラパンドラ 秘密のオブジェ
Pandora, Pandora, an object of secrets
可能性が スリリングインアファイト
Possibility is thrilling in a fight
幾層にも重なって 停滞と歪みにアンビバレンス
Layered many times over, ambivalence in stagnation and distortion
振り解いた 宿命向かい風
Shaking off the headwind of fate
Scarab 今こそ刹那の願い 打ち鳴らせ Wake Up!
Scarab, now is the time for a fleeting wish, sound the alarm, Wake Up!
そっと手を伸ばす
Gently reaching out a hand
冬枯れの結晶
Crystals of winter witheredness
閉ざしてしまいそうな夜だって
Even on nights that seem to close in
この歌声で繋ぎ止めてみせるから
I'll show you I can hold it together with this voice
風が刻む 涙のメロディ
The wind carves a melody of tears
パンドラパンドラ 夢を掘り舞い
Pandora, Pandora, digging up and dancing with dreams
移ろい色褪せぬように
So as not to fade and change
パンドラパンドラ 秘密のオブジェ
Pandora, Pandora, an object of secrets
Scarab 嗚呼 パンパンパンパンパン
Scarab, ah, pan-pan-pan-pan-pan
灯す火が サイレンスプラウト
The lighting fire, Silent Sprout
Scarab
無料パートは終了いたしました。
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended.
Thank you for watching!
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching!